(Leonard:)On a road.
(Leonard:)Wasn't even that
hard to find.
This is so amazing!
I know!
(Leonard:)You want to
get a picture?
(Sheldon:)I want more than a picture.
(Sheldon:)I want to go in.
(Leonard:)Well, so do I, but
they'll never let us.
(Sheldon:)Is that the attitude
that helped you get Penny?
(Leonard:)No, but I don't have three years
(Leonard:)to make that gate
feel sorry for me.
Uh, there's
a speaker box.
(Sheldon:)Drive up, push the button,
and let's see what happens.
(Leonard:)Okay, yeah.
(Leonard:)What do we
have to lose?
(Leonard:)I'm a little nervous.
(Sheldon:)Well, get over it.
(Sheldon:)Confidence is key
in these situations.
(Sheldon:)Right.
(gasps) You pushed it--
are you out of your mind?!